

Córdoba, Argentina

26 years old

Argentine

03517619357

Languages

Spanish

Native

English

B2

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Typescript

React.js

Next.js

Node.js

Express

Social networks

@JulianOviedo

in @julian-oviedo-17b605136/

Julian Oviedo

Software Developer [Front-End]

About me

My name is Julian, I'm 26 years old. I'm currently studying Computer Science since almost 3 years and also have an Accountant degree. As you can see, I really like maths and everything related with numbers.

I'm a software developer with solid professional experience building web applications. My main focus is on the front-end, but i love building and learning about both ends of the stacks. I consider myself a very capable person to achieve everything i propose to and always want to learn new things. I think i only need the oportunity to introduce myself and show what I'm worth.

Portfolio > https://julianoviedo-portfolio.vercel.app/

Work experience

Software Developer

Since January 2022 Solvd Inc Remote

React Javascript Intern

From June 2022 to December 2022 Solvd Inc. Remote Content and progress

https://github.com/qaprosoft/react-laba-arg-1

Accountant

From August 2021 to January CEFyT - Centro de Estudios Filosóficos y Teológicos Cordoba, 2022 Argentina

Financial and Tax Management of the entity - Administrative staff management (two people in charge) - Settlement of assets - Accounting and financial advice.

Accounting analyst

From June 2017 to August 2021 Instituto Parroquial Ceferino Namuncurá Cordoba, Argentina Analysis of checking accounts - Accounting - Bank reconciliations - Settlement of salaries of teaching and non-teaching staff - Purchases - Payment to suppliers - Budget control - Assistance in the preparation of the accounting balance

Formation

Public Accountant

From January 2018 to June 2022 Universidad Empresarial Siglo XXI Argentina

Computer science

From January 2020 to June 2024 Universidad Empresarial Siglo XXI Argentina

Web Developer Bootcamp 2022

From January 2022 to May 2022 Udemy

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-bfbdfda5-0b94-4cb5-b7f3-df78470f048a/